{
    "id": "5c6bbccf617a4759acf39c5ccc4e3de3",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He …………………. at six o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is getting up",
                "gets up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0724a3ad587446e68d56f6c28266d94a"
        },
        {
            "question": "God ……………….. us all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loves",
                "is loving",
                "love"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4af782eb81044bd28bcdeb3602722b44"
        },
        {
            "question": "My dad ………………… for Delhi tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaves",
                "is leaving",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6946c1b9d39845e4bfd9a8add3b7dc2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… a book now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "reads",
                "is reading"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27f30ae000b04045aaef749d1dabac64"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. just ……………….. a call from him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am, receiving",
                "have, received",
                "have, been receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e107fb1d71b455aa2c47d8f272518ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………….. each other for five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "are knowing",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ecb2d35709b844678318b56a4526fbd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… the Eiffel Tower.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a1e47455f5146ff8ec036637c012fdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… in Singapore since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "has been working",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "480bcb8397dd48a29b22d1ea58f7c092"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train ………………… five hours late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "is arrived",
                "has been arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "618b9eba193b4bb7b747fd200eb13133"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was a student, I ……………….. hard to pay my tuition fee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "worked",
                "have worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8422e251439043a18da9bd9e81ea415e"
        }
    ]
}